canaca.com 2014-02-09

# Canaca.com Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY - COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY**

This site is owned and operated by Canaca-com Inc. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At Canaca, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.  

**Canaca's Privacy Policy is organized along ten privacy principles, which are:**

1\. Accountability  
2\. Identifying Purposes  
3\. Consent  
4\. Limiting Collection  
5\. Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention  
6\. Accuracy  
7\. Safeguards  
8\. Openness  
9\. Individual Access  
10\. Challenging Compliance 

Because we gather certain types of information about our members, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it. 

**INFORMATION Canaca GATHERS AND TRACKS**

Canaca gathers two types of information about users: 

* Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in our message boards or forums, to email a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys or to order any service: 

* Information Canaca gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. Under no circumstances does Canaca divulge any information about an individual user to a third party except to it's sister company Acanac Inc. . 

Canaca-com Inc. Gathers User Information In The Following Processes: 

Optional Voluntary Information 

We offer the services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

**Privacy Policy**

**1\. Electronic newsletters policy (Dispatches)**

We will offer a free electronic newsletter to users. Canaca gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe to our service. 

**2\. Message boards/forums policy**

Users of the site's Message Boards and Forums must register separately for these services (both are free of charge) in order to post messages, although they needn't register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address. 

**3\. "E-mail this to a friend" policy**

Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking "e-mail this to a friend". The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose. 

**4\. Polling**

We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user. Canaca may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users. 

**5\. Surveys**

Canaca-com Inc. may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our services to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with Canaca-com Inc. our sister company. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any other third party. 

**Usage tracking**

Canaca tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users Canaca does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser). 

Canaca sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. 

**Cookies**

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply your self. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Canaca uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling and surveys. 

How the information you gather is used if relevent. 

**USE OF INFORMATION**

Canaca uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience with our service, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future services. 

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, message boards, and forums. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. Canaca never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners except with Canaca-com Inc. 

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like, and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters. 

**SECURITY**

Canaca operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. 

**YOUR CONSENT**

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Canaca. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**For More Information**  
If you have questions or concerns about your privacy, you can contact us by email or snail mail at 

privacy@canaca.com

Address  
1650 Dundas Street East. Unit 203  
Mississauga, Ontario L4X 2Z3  
Canada
